(RASPY BREATHING)
(SNARLING)
ANDREA: Almost done.
(SIGHS)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
ANDREA: Here.
If only we had some cab'. (SOFT CHUCKLE)
Girls' night.
-(CHAINS RATTLING)
-(ZOMBIES SNARLING)
Boys are getting restless again.
You still haven't told me,
where did you find them?
Did they attack? Did you hunt them down?
Or did you know them?
I'm so sorry.
Oh, God.
(SNIFFLES)
You want to talk about it?
Okay.
They deserved what they got.
They weren't human to begin with.
(METAL CLANKING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
-You, grab the .50.
-You got it.
The Governor wants all this?
He wants options.
Where is he now?
MARTINEZ: Not here.
-How many are going out?
-Everybody.
I thought there was a deal on the table.
I'm sure it's just a precaution,
a show of force.
(SNIFFLES)
Milton.
Milton!
You need something?
What is that?
It's my workshop.
How does that help Woodbury?
Excuse me?
This was supposed to be
a new start, a way out.
What about everything we talked about?
Beating this thing? Clawing our way back?
Look, this business with Michonne,
I understand.
-But the people at the prison...
-What?
Hmm?
-I should move on?
-Yes.
Well, I will as soon as this is over.
-Philip...
-Let me ask you something, huh?
Do you still believe the biters
have some spark in them, huh?
Of who they were?
I think so.
Then that was my daughter, wasn't it?
Whether that was Penny or not,
it's done.
-It doesn't matter.
-Oh...
It's all that matters.
There is no deal.
Philip's asked for Michonne.
Rick would never agree to that.
Whether he hands her over or not,
he's gonna kill them all.
(SIGHS)
-I have to stop this.
-I don't think you can.
MILTON: Leave.
Tell the people at the prison
to get out of there.
In time, he'll move on.
No.
I have to kill him.
You'll never get close to him.
They'll gun you down first.
Only if they see me coming.
Milton, this is sick.
-I can't just stand back and watch...
-(DOOR OPENS)
(FLOOR CREAKS)
(WHISTLING)
(TAPE REWINDING)
(WHISTLING ON TAPE)
(REWINDING)
(WHISPERING) No!
(CLANKING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(EXHALES)
(PANTING)
How can you still protect him?
He doesn't give a shit about you.
I knew Philip before
he became The Governor.
That man still exists.
I don't believe that.
Okay, so you kill The Governor.
Then you get shot,
then Martinez takes over. What then?
(SIGHS)
Killing The Governor
doesn't save your friends.
-Then I have to go back. Warn them.
-Mmm.
-And you're coming with me.
-I can't leave Woodbury.
You really want to be a part of this?
I don't know anyone at the prison.
So what? You know Merle. He fit in.
You'll be fine.
Like it or not, I belong here.
Then if you stay,
you can't keep looking the other way.
Take care of yourself.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
You got any other weapons?
-Any ammo for this?
-Yeah.
Hey. Do you have more rounds?
What do you guys got?
-Thanks.
-MARTINEZ: Andrea.
Andrea!
Governor wants all weapons collected.
Got to get the team geared up.
I think I'm more helpful armed.
Hand over your piece and any ammo.
No.
Let's not be stupid about this.
Hand over your piece.
You got a knife?
You want to frisk me?
I should have told you about all this.
I'm sorry.
I just, uh...
I want to keep you separate from this.
Safe.
-You understand?
-Yeah.
-I just want to help.
-Well, you can.
Tomorrow.
I want you with us
when we go and meet Rick.
He tries anything,
you can talk some sense into him.
Tries anything?
Well, you trust them, I don't.
Understood.
I'll be there.
-You take this one.
-(WALKER SNARLING)
You need the practice.
Just relax.
How am I gonna relax
if you keep telling me to relax?
(SIGHS)
Wasn't even close.
-You want to do this?
-I have been.
You're wasting ammo.
Got him.
Nice shot.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, large pack of walkers
was spotted heading for the main wall.
Martinez wants some help.
I got this covered.
We're not supposed to leave this post.
Ask Martinez.
I'm just doing what I'm told.
TYREESE: You got to bring him over.
We need to hear it from him.
-You're wasting time.
-SASHA: Why can't you handle it?
You're supposed to be a good shot.
(MAN YELLING)
-What are you doing?
-ANDREA: I've got to get out of here.
-TYREESE: Nobody leaves.
-Please, I don't want any trouble.
-What is this about?
-Just get out of my way.
-You'll get killed out there.
-Don't.
Relax.
Nobody's got to get hurt here.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, it's just this place is...
-I can't stay here.
-Why?
The Governor,
he is not what he seems to be.
-He seems pretty straight up to me.
-Yeah, that's what I thought, too.
But I'm telling you,
he has done terrible things.
He's planning worse.
I got to get out of here
and you should, too.
Look, you're rattled, exhausted.
Just put the knife down.
I'm going.
Okay.
(GROANS)
SASHA: We shouldn't have let her go.
What do you want me to do, shoot her?
-MARTINEZ: You should have stopped her.
-Stop her how?
-Shoot her in the back?
-No, you did the right thing.
Thank God neither of you were hurt, huh.
We stand on that wall to stop biters,
not keep people in.
This isn't a prison camp, is it?
Of course not. It's just
she's in no shape to take care of herself.
Seems pretty capable to me.
She was out there all winter.
Alone.
Can you imagine?
Now, you two had each other
or your friends.
She only had the biters.
And we brought her in, tried to help her,
but it was too late.
She'd been out there too long.
Did she... Did she say anything?
-Like what?
-I don't know. Like what panicked her?
No.
I hope this doesn't affect us.
What do you mean?
Well, we heard she was
with that prison group.
-I hope I didn't complicate things.
-No. No.
Um, look, I'll tell you what, um...
Martinez here could use
a hand with something.
If you wouldn't mind helping him out,
I'd appreciate it.
-Of course.
-Thank you.
(DOOR OPENS)
Is she gone?
They going after her?
No.
I am.
Oh.
You have a problem with that, too?
Let her go.
Why would I do that?
She just wants to be with her people.
-You talked to her?
-No.
You did.
You knew she was leaving, didn't you?
She told me.
What else did you two talk about, huh?
Did you tell her about the deal?
Did you tell her about Michonne?
(SHUDDERING)
She knows, doesn't she?
(PANTING)
(WALKERS GROWLING)
Hey.
Be ready to roll in a few.
Where to?
We're not going after that girl, are we?
What if we were? Is that a problem?
She was pretty shook up.
She definitely didn't want to be here.
Look, she's on her own, understood?
We got something else.
It's sort of hard to explain.
Just be at the truck in five.
-Okay.
-ALLEN: What girl?
Andrea jumped the wall.
ALLEN: On your watch?
And you let her go?
Hey, man, these guys have been talking.
She's trouble.
Well, maybe she's not the issue.
She said some pretty crazy shit.
You know why? 'Cause she's crazy.
Hey, don't screw this up for us.
-I'm just looking out.
-For you two, maybe.
-What the hell are you talking about?
-We got a good thing here.
I don't want to get tossed out
because of you.
These guys are on edge.
They've been attacked by that crazy-ass
cowboy and some chick with a sword.
Shit's going down and you're making waves.
We just have to get with the program.
I am.
Okay, that guy doesn't trust you.
-Do not screw this up.
-Ease back, man.
Or what? You gonna shame me
in front of my boy again?
Don't go there, man.
Donna...
(SIGHS) I just happened to be there.
-It could have been anyone.
-But it wasn't, was it?
-It was you.
-You want to do this now?
A long time coming.
You guys catch up.
Come on, Ben.
Yeah, it was me. I saved her life.
Right place, right time.
And from that moment,
she was glued to you like a lost puppy.
Her knight in shining armor.
It made me feel like...
-I could have done it.
-I know you could've.
-She didn't.
-Of course she did.
She knew that.
She was just scared, that's all.
This ain't got nothing
to do with you or me.
Yo, I said five.
Let's go. Fire it up.
-We ain't done.
-(ENGINE STARTS)
(PANTING)
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
-(SNARLING)
-(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
SASHA: What is that?
MARTINEZ: Jackpot, baby.
This some kind of extermination?
You could say that.
No weeding out today, Shump.
-The more the merrier.
-All right.
You got a use for them?
Honey, we got a use for everything.
(SNARLING)
This got something to do
with that meeting tomorrow?
The one with the prison group?
Ho, ho, ho. Give that man a prize.
-You're bringing biters?
-Allen, heads up.
Okay, this is genius.
Hey, kid, grab the collars
out of the truck.
This ain't right.
Didn't think we were gonna
have any problems today, fella.
I didn't think we'd be
feeding people to biters.
What do you care? They're rats.
This is sick.
ALLEN: Hey, give me a hand here.
Ty, you deaf?
I'm not doing this.
They got women and children.
You can't do this.
All right, suit yourself.
We get back, you tell The Governor.
He'll send you packing.
Send you all packing.
There's no need for that. Damn it.
Relax. We looked out for each other.
We'll do it again.
We'll get out of your way
if that's what you want.
You don't speak for us.
You're not sending my boy out there again.
-I look out for him.
-Like you looked out for Donna?
(GRUNTS)
-SASHA: Tyreese!
-Leave him alone!
Get off me!
(SNARLING)
Do it.
Go on!
Please.
(GRUNTS)
You okay?
(CLAPPING)
You've all been very productive.
Shump, take 'em back to town.
Let 'em do some knitting.
(SIGHS)
(PANTING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Oh, God. Okay.
(HORN HONKING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(PANTING)
(TRUCK APPROACHES)
(TRUCK ENGINE RUNNING)
-(CLATTERS)
-Shit.
-(ENGINE TURNS OFF)
-(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CLATTERING)
(WHISTLING)
(SNARLING)
(FENCE RATTLES)
(CLATTERING)
(SOFTLY) Andrea.
Come back with me. Come back to Woodbury.
We need you. We all need you.
That's your home now.
Your people.
Your town.
You can't just leave 'em all behind.
Please, Andrea, come home.
Suit yourself.
(ANDREA GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RATTLING)
(SHUDDERING)
(FENCE RATTLES)
(WHISTLING)
(SHOVEL SCRAPING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(SNARLING)
(GRUNTS)
(SHOVEL BANGING)
(FENCE RATTLES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CLANGING)
(SNARLING)
Time to go home, huh?
Andrea.
(SNARLING)
(GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOTS)
(FIRING CONTINUES)
-(GUN CLICKS)
-(SHOUTS)
(THE GOVERNOR YELLING)
(SNARLING)
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(GROWLING)
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
Shh.
Yeah.
(MOANING)
Did you find her?
No luck.
Just got word.
Someone barbecued the pit biters.
Who?
Got a few shit-stirrers in the bunch.
-Tyreese and his sister.
-(SIGHS)
Send them over to distro.
-Rest of the group, too.
-All right.
We're gonna need biters, so get some more.
All right, you got it.
(DOOR OPENS)
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Did you find her?
No.
Hardly made it back myself.
I'll look again tomorrow.
So I heard there was
a little hang-up at the pits.
You got a beef with Rick,
that's fair enough.
But you can't be feeding
his kids to biters.
No one's feeding anyone to biters.
Well, I saw the trailers.
No, it's a scare tactic. It's a bluff.
I'd rather scare his people
into leaving us alone
than engaging in another fight.
I'm trying to save lives here.
They're just for show?
You know, people are more
afraid of a biter on a leash
than a gun in their face.
It's pretty effective.
Then why didn't your man just say that?
'Cause...
We don't discuss tactics with people
that we don't really know.
(SIGHS)
Governor, look.
I shoot my mouth off sometimes,
but the truth is we want to stay.
I saw red. It won't happen again.
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
Where did you get the gasoline?
Come again?
Doesn't matter.
Is she dead?
I hope not.
Are you okay?
Never been better.
It's a real shame about the pits.
You heard about that, huh?
I hope you find out who did it.
Already have.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)